http://www.doogeveneers.com/content/privacy-policy

menu
Browse VeneersRequest SamplesBe InspiredBe SupportedSpecify VeneerFeatured ProductsContact UsOur TeamShowroom
Main menuBrowseVeneersBeSupportedBeInspiredSpecifyVeneerFeaturedProductsSearch
Published May 24, 2018
Introduction
We take care to protect the privacy of customers and users of doogeveneers.com. This privacy policy explains how we collect, store and use data about you.
Cookies
During normal use of doogeveneers.com we collect and store statistical information to analyse how parts of this website are used. This data is anonymous and contains no personally identifiable data about you. For more information see Google Analytics Cookie Usage on Websites.
Personal data you submit
On our contact page within the website you have the option to submit personal information to us so that we might send you further information.
Third parties
We will not disclose any personal information we collect about you to a third party without your consent. In connection with any application, request or enquiry you make, your information will be passed directly to the relevant contact within the company.
By submitting your personal information through this website, you are consenting to it being processed by Dooge Veneers in the manner described above.
Further details
If you have submitted personal information through this website and wish us to cease using it for the purposes described above, please contact us.
If you require clarity or further information, please contact us:
https://doogeveneers.com/contact-us
tel: (616) 698-6450
